Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  2/16/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  1/30/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  2/19/57. Issue: rates of pay - vacation relief
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  9/7/56. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  9/7/56. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  4/10/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  11/2/56. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  4/12/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  11/2/56. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  4/15/57. Issue: seniority - probationary employees
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  4/30/57. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  5/31/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  3/7/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  3/7/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  6/29/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  3/8/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  7/1/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - qualifications
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  7/3/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  3/28/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  3/28/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  3/29/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  3/29/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  7/5/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  7/6/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  1/8/58. Issue: Assignment of jobs - overtime.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  7/8/57. Issue: transfers
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  7/10/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  4/17/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  4/17/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  7/15/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  7/12/57. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  3/24/58. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  2/28/58. Issue: vacation pay - computation
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  1/16/58. Issue: grievance and grievance procedure
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  8/7/57. Issue: transfers -overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  10/5/57. Issue: discharge
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  3/31/58. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  9/27/59. Issue: transfers
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 6a)
  6/61. No award
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co. Miscellaneous papers (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
- Alpha Portland Cement Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers' Int'l Union (CLGW), Local 7, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  10/16/60. Issue: rates of pay.
- Alton Box Board Co., Alton, Illinois vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers (UPP), AFL-CIO. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Settled
- Alton Box Board Co., Alton, Illinois vs. Alton Paperworkers Union, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  2/3/60. Issue: layoff.
- Alton Box Board Co., Alton, Illinois vs. UPP, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  8/18/68. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Alton Box Board Co., Galesburg, Illinois vs. UPP, AFL-CIO, Local 643, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  1/28/63. Issue: assignment of jobs, overtime
- Alton Box Board Co., Pacific, Missouri vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, Local 490, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  8/15/64. Issue: overtime - refusal of overtime
- Aluminum Company of America, Rosiclare, Illinois vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America (UMW), Local 12,590, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  2/7/63. Issue: rates of pay - Saturday, Sunday, holiday work
- Alvey, Inc., St. Louis County, Missouri vs. IBT, Local 688, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  6/20/74. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Alvey, Inc., St. Louis County, Missouri vs. IBT, Local 688, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  8/16/74. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Alvey, Inc., St. Louis County, Missouri vs. IBT, Local 688, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  11/6/74. Issue: discipline - suspension - discharge
- American Air Filter Co., Inc. vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers (BBF), Lodge 1012, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  9/24/64. Issue: strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - breach of no-strike clause
- American Air Filter Co., Inc. vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers (BBF), Lodge 1013, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  9/24/64. Issue: strikes - wildcat strikes. (Continued in Box 16 ff 1 and 2.)
- American Air Filter Co., Inc. vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers (BBF), Lodge 1014, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  Issue: strikes - wildcat strikes. (Continued from Box 15.)
- American Air Filter Co., Inc. vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers (BBF), Lodge 1015, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  2/24/75. Issue: discipline - discharge
- American Bosch Arma Mississippi Corp., Drawer 1111, Columbus, Mississippi vs. IUE, AFL-CIO, Local 794, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  1/23/60. Issue: overtime
- American Bosch Arma Mississippi Corp., Drawer 1111, Columbus, Mississippi vs. IUE, AFL-CIO, Local 795, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  1/24/60. Issue: layoff - failure to recall
- American Bosch Arma Mississippi Corp., Drawer 1111, Columbus, Mississippi vs. IUE, AFL-CIO, Local 796, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  1/25/60. Issue: seniority
- American Bosch Arma Mississippi Corp., Drawer 1111, Columbus, Mississippi vs. IUE, AFL-CIO, Local 797, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  1/27/60. Issue: reduction in force - assignment of jobs
- American Bosch Arma Mississippi Corp., Drawer 1111, Columbus, Mississippi vs. IUE, AFL-CIO, Local 798, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  1/28/60. Issue: reduction in force - assignment of jobs
- American Bosch Arma Mississippi Corp., Drawer 1111, Columbus, Mississippi vs. IUE, AFL-CIO, Local 799 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Correspondence re previous 5 cases
- American Brake Shoe Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Int'l. Molders' and Foundry Workers Union of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 59, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  4/17/61. Issue: discipline - layoff; layoff - holidays - holiday pay
- American Brands, American Cigar Division vs. Tobacco Workers Int'l. Union (TWIU), AFL-CIO, Local 316., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  2/20/71. Issue: classification of jobs - added duties
- American Buslines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union (ATU), AFL-CIO, Division 1133., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  7/3/73. Issue: arbitrability; discipline - discharge
- American Can Corp., Marathon Southern Corp. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 966, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  10/12/64. Issue: overtime
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen (BRC), Lodge 343, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  7/8/68. Issue: demotion - discipline
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. USA, Local 2409, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  4/16/48. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. USA, Local 2409, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  6/14/53. Issue: discipline - layoff; work assignment.
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. USA, Local 2409, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  3/22/54. Issue: layoff - seniority
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. USA, Local 2409, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  5/5/54. Issue: bargaining unit - transfer of work
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. USA, Local 2409, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  11/25/55. Issue: promotion - seniority
- American Car and Foundry Co. vs. USA, Local 2409, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  12/13/48. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- American Car and Foundry vs. BRC, Local 365, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  11/27/64. Issue: discharge - discipline - insubordination
- American Car and Foundry vs. BRC, Local 365, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  7/12/66. Issue: discharge - discipline
- American Car and Foundry vs. BRC, Local 365, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  4/1/68. Withdrawn
- American Car and Foundry vs. BRC, Local 365, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  2/7/69. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay
- American Foundry and Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 1377, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  5/2/49. Issue: layoff - discharge
- American Hospital Supply Corp. vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU) Local 258, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  11/6/69. Issue: classification of jobs - creation of new classification
- American Machine and Foundry Co. vs. Int'l. Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Local 1033, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  10/4/71. Issue: discharge - leaving plant without permission
- American National Stores, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  4/12/73. Issue: discharge
- American Oil Co. vs. Independent Oil Workers Union, Local 117, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  9/23/62. Issue: call in - sick leave
- American Oil Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-672, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  3/14/66. Issue: assignment of jobs - rates of pay
- American Oil Co. vs. Office Employees Association, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  2/8/64. Issue: posting vacancies
- American Oil Co. vs. Independent Oil Workers Union, Local 115, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  11/20/61. Issue: assignment of jobs
- American Oil Co. vs. Independent Oil Workers Union, Local 115, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  10/25/61. Issue: rate of pay
- American Oil Co. vs. Independent Oil Workers Union, Local 115, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  11/11/61. Issue: assignment of overtime
- American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp. vs. Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers, Local 1, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  8/31/65. Issue: assignment of jobs
- American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp. vs. United Association of Journeyman and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry (PPF), Local 522, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  1/14/69. Issue: promotion - seniority
- American Steel Foundries, East St. Louis, Illinois vs. USA, CIO, Local 1038, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  7/9/53. Issue: assignment of jobs
- American Steel Foundries, Inc., Granite City, Illinois vs. USA, Local 1063, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  6/19/53. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- American Steel Foundries, Inc., Granite City, Illinois vs. USA, Local 1063, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  7/14/59. Issue: assignment of jobs - de minimis assignment
- American Sugar Refining Co. vs. United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1101, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  7/10/65. Issue: assignment of jobs - shift scheduling
- American Thermometer Co. vs. USA, Local 1979, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  11/14/47. Issue: rates of pay - Saturday, Sunday and holiday work
- American Thermometer Co. vs. USA, Local 1979, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  5/17/50. Issue: discipline - discharge
- American Thermometer Co. vs. USA, Local 1979, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  8/25-26/51. Issue: transfers
- American Thermometer Co. vs. USA, Local 1979, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  6/23/53. Issue: transfer - seniority
- American Thermometer Division, Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Co. vs. USA, Local 4678, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  8/12/54. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- American Thermometer Division, Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Co. vs. USA, Local 1979, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  12/27/49. Issue: vacations - eligibility
- American Walnut Co. vs. Int'l. Woodworkers of America (IWA), Local 5-266, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  9/2/64. Issue: discipline - discharge
- American Zinc Co. of Illinois vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, AFL, Local 1201, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  8/11/51. Issue: rates of pay
- American Zinc Co. of Illinois vs. OCAW, AFL-CIO, Local 7-347, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  11/25/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Ampco Metal, Inc, Milwaukee, Wisconsin vs. UAW, AFL-CIO, Local 115, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  10/25/57. Issue: arbitrability
- Anchor Hocking Glass Corp. vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada (GBBA), Local 139, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  7/18/69. Issue: discipline - warnings
- Anderson, Clayton and Co., Foods Division vs. Int'l. Chemical Workers' Union (ICW), Local 635, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  2/20/58. Issue: overtime
- Anderson, Clayton and Co., Foods Division vs. Int'l. Chemical Workers' Union (ICW), Local 635, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  3/5/67. Issue: schedules of work - change of schedule
- Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. Int'l. Union of United Brewery, Cereal, Flour, Distillery and Soft Drink Workers of America, CIO, Local 187, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  5/10/54. Issue: Discipline - negligence and carelessness
- Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. Int'l. Union of United Brewery, Cereal, Flour, Distillery and Soft Drink Workers of America, CIO, Local 262, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  11/29/63. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Anlin Co. of Illinois vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers (IBFO), AFL-CIO, Local 46, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  8/9/61. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Appleton Coated Paper Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 15,014, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  3/6/62. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Archer-Daniels-Midland Co. vs. American Federation of Grain Millers (AFGM) Local 16, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  6/30/64. Issue: discharge - discipline - sleeping on job
- ArkeTex Ceramic Corp. vs. United Brick and Clay Workers (UBCW), Local 527, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  3/30/63. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Armco Steel Corp., Union Wire vs. USA, Local 5109, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  6/25/62. Issue: discharge - drinking on the job
- Armco Steel Corp. vs. USA, Local 13, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  12/17/62. Issue: assignment of jobs - crew size
- Armco Steel Corp. vs. Armco Employees Independent Federation, Inc, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  3/2/68. Issue: overtime - assignment
- Armco Steel Corp. vs. USA, Local 5109, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Armor Elevator Co. vs. IBEW, Local 369, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  9/18/73. Issue: strike
- Armor Elevator Co. vs. IBEW, Local 369, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  6/22/72. Issue: suspension - safety equipment
- Armor Elevator Co. vs. IBEW, Local 369, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  9/18/73. Issue: strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - discipline
- Armour and Co. vs. Packinghouse Chauffeurs and Salesmen of Food Products Union, IBT, Local 700, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  7/5/72. Issue: assignment of jobs - past practice
- Armour Pharmaceutical Co. vs. ICW, Local 498, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  5/9/68. Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit
- Armstrong Cork Co. vs. GBBA, AFL-CIO, Local 96, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  8/17/66. Issue: schedules of work - continuous operation - lunch periods
- Armstrong Cork Co. - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Arrow Transportation Co. vs. Marine Officers Association, IBT, Local 54, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  11/18/68. Issue: bumping - seniority
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Fayette, Alabama vs. UAW, Local 759, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  3/27/69. Issue: discipline - restriction of production
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Greenwood, Indiana vs. IAM, Local 1208 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  No decision
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Greenwood, Indiana vs. IAM, Local 1208, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  8/20/73. Issue: shift scheduling
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Indianapolis, Indiana vs. IAM, Local 1208 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Monroeville, Alabama vs. USA, Local 7757, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  5/12/71. Issue: rates of pay
- Arvin Industries, Inc., North Vernon, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 301 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Princeton, Kentucky vs. IAM, Local 888, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 13-15)
  11/28/71. Issue: reduction in force - demotions
- Arvin Industries, Inc., Columbus, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 97, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  2/28/63. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Arvin Industries, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 97 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Asphaltic Concrete Corp. vs. IBT, Local 682., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  4/13/61. No decision
- Associated General Contractors of St. Louis vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, AFL, Local 42, 53, and 110 and the Eastern Missouri Laborers District Council, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  12/18/52. Issue: rates of pay
- Associated General Contractors of St. Louis vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, AFL, Local 42, 53, and 110 and the Eastern Missouri Laborers District Council, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  8/22/58. Issue: shift scheduling
- Associated General Contractors of St. Louis vs. Hoisting Engineers, Local 513 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  Withdrawn
- Associated Retailers Suburban Delivery Co. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  12/11/71. Issue: termination - illness, reporting
- Associated Spring Corp. vs. USA, Local 6127, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  1/12/62. Issue: rates of pay - job classification
- Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Association (RCIA), Local 1130, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  11/15/65. Issue: schedules of work - reduction of hours
- Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union, Local 1, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  12/5/71. Issue: schedules of work - work week
- Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America (MCBW), 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  4/5/62. Issue: discharge - negligence
- Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs. RCIA, Local 536., 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  8/18/73. Issue: assignment of jobs - change in location
- Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 418, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  9/23/74. Issue: rates of pay
- Atlas Chemical Industries vs. UMW, District 50, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  6/24/68. No award in file
- Atlas Tool and Manufacturing Co. vs. Roy Gerling, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  7/29/69. Issue: termination - benefits
- AutoLite (Electric) Co. vs. UAW, Local 675., 1956 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  3/7/56. Issue: overtime - assignment of.
- Auffenberg, Bob, Buick, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 604, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  2/26/60. Issue: rates of pay
- Avco Broadcasting Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 1224, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  8/3/66. Issue: illness - compensation
- Avsco, Inc. vs. Springs Independent Plastics Union, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  8/22/72. Issue: discipline - plant rules
- Ball Brothers Co. vs. United Glass and Ceramic Workers (UGCW), Local 93, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  12/15/55. Issue: discharge - insubordination
- Banquet Foods Corp. vs. IBT, Local 535, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  3/19/73. Issue: discharge - excessive absences
- Basler Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 840, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  3/20/60. Issue: seniority
- Basler Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 840, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  7/9/65. Issue: no award
- Baughman Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 4817, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  4/26/56. Issue: absences - reporting
- Bemis Brothers Bag Co. vs. TWUA, Local 1426, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  8/17/59. Issue: discharge - negligence
- Bemis Brothers Bag Co. vs. TWUA, Local 375, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  5/21/61. Issue: discipline - layoff- insubordination